<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Dev Logs on JR0.org</title><link>https://jr0.org/devlogs/</link><description>Recent content in Dev Logs on JR0.org</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://jr0.org/devlogs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>April 2022 - Local List Business Pitch</title><link>https://jr0.org/devlogs/april-2022/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://jr0.org/devlogs/april-2022/</guid><description>On April 21st, the whole Local List team (Me and 4 others) got to present our business to our town&amp;rsquo;s chamber of commerce. Our idea and demo was met with lots of excitement and great feedback. The day after, we got to pitch our idea to more business owners during our school&amp;rsquo;s business project&amp;rsquo;s night event. We won the event&amp;rsquo;s Judges award for our idea and presentation. The current site can be found at thelocallist.</description></item><item><title>August 2022</title><link>https://jr0.org/devlogs/august-2022/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://jr0.org/devlogs/august-2022/</guid><description>Work I just finished a month of work at Lucid Automation. I have been working with Go using Gin-Gonic and React JS. I have also been working with Keras and Tensorflow in Python. It has been an amazing experience and I have learned tons already.
Hackathons In this month, I also did two hackathons, Plant Here and Future Fire Finder.
1. Plant Here 🌿 The first was a project called Plant here.</description></item><item><title>February 2022 - Creating Dev Log Page</title><link>https://jr0.org/devlogs/february-2022/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://jr0.org/devlogs/february-2022/</guid><description>This months has been pretty interesting. I have learned several things like how to use Gatsby and GraphQL. I have been working on auto-clock-speed a lot, and I 0.1.8 was released! I have also been writing code for the Hermes project. This months I picked up the book &amp;lsquo;Design Patterns&amp;rsquo; and it&amp;rsquo;s great. Something that I have been using more often is React. Sometimes I forget how useful a good frontend framework can be.</description></item><item><title>July 2022</title><link>https://jr0.org/devlogs/july-2022/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://jr0.org/devlogs/july-2022/</guid><description>This month, I made 231 commits in 30 different repositories. One of my favorite projects was BestNextStep which was a project that I thought of many years ago but was not able to fully develop until the last few years. I have also been working on a math paper with the current (tentative to change) title of Observations of Every Third Digit of the Thue-Morse Sequence. This month I created 11 repositories, two are cli applications in Go.</description></item><item><title>June 2022 - Go, C, and Rust!</title><link>https://jr0.org/devlogs/june-2022/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://jr0.org/devlogs/june-2022/</guid><description>This month I have committed to keeping up three system languages (Go, Rust, C) to learn more about backend tools and system programs. I also keep up my skills with Python because it is a great language to know. I made a library called Sense and wrote it in Go, Rust, C, and Python. I also wrote a preprocesor for Go in Go called Macaroon. I also wrote a study tool called study-cli in Go as well.</description></item><item><title>March 2022 - Starting Local List</title><link>https://jr0.org/devlogs/march-2022/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://jr0.org/devlogs/march-2022/</guid><description>This month, I registered the domains finditlocal.org and finditlocal.us for a company called Local List I started in connection with my Econ class. I created a frontend using React and a backend using Django. Currently, both are hosted and communicating to display local products at those domains. I am really excited for this project and I even printed business cards and stickers for the project to share with classmates. I feel like this project is the latest culmination of my skills in frontend, backend, and system architecture.</description></item><item><title>May 2022 - Da Vinci Game Jam &amp; More Auto Clock Speed</title><link>https://jr0.org/devlogs/may-2022/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://jr0.org/devlogs/may-2022/</guid><description>This month I had my finals and AP tests, all of which where a lot of work, but I still worked on some project and organized the first annual Da Vinci Game Jam for my school. Links to the resources for the workshops can be found here. The game jam was an overall success and we had many great game entries. This month I also worked on auto clock speed some more, adding a universal interface to all of the commands and other issues.</description></item><item><title>September 2022</title><link>https://jr0.org/devlogs/september-2022/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://jr0.org/devlogs/september-2022/</guid><description>T3 research I finished the first draft of my collaborative paper, titled Observations on Every Third Digit of the Thue-Morse Sequence. It is still waiting peer review, but all of the content is finished.
Abstract We investigate some interesting properties of the sequence made up of every third term of the Thue-Morse sequence, and consider other similar sequences.
The paper can be found at jr0.org/research/t3.
Follow up paper The same people involved in t3 will continue to work on a follow up paper that takes a similar problems into consideration.</description></item></channel></rss>